Guide to the International Brigades Archive, Moscow: Selected Images ALBA.PHOTO.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Folder 197: Album of 15th International Brigade Presented to the American Communist Volunteers of the 15th Brigade by the Communist Party of Spain (Postcards, Drawings, and Signatures), Oct 1938
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197037)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/37
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197038)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/38
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197039)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/39
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197040)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/40
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197041)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/41
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197042)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/42
  - [Julio Antonio Mella], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197043)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/43
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197044)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/44
  - [Luis Carlos Prestes], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197045)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/45
  - ["Promesa"], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197046)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/46
  - [Drawing: soldiers with rifles], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197047)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/47
  - ["Declaration of the American Negro Comrades"], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197048)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/48
  - [Declaration continued with signatures of African-Americans], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197049)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/49
  - [Slogan: "Espana para el pueblo, el pueblo para Espana"], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197050)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/50
  - [International Brigades Logo, "Foto-Dan Kraman"], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197051)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/51
- Folder 198: Photographs of Newspapers, Posters and Stands in the 15th International Brigade
  - [Notice posted on bullet-ridden wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 177_198003)
    Moscow Number: 5/198/3
  - [Man looking at wall newspaper], undated (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 177_198004)
    Moscow Number: 5/198/4
  - "Contra Aviones, Grupos de Activistas," Poster by Antonio Pujol, undated (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 177_198005)
    Moscow Number: 5/198/5
  - Wall Newspaper of the 15th International Brigade Anti-Tank Battery, undated (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 177_198006)
    Moscow Number: 5/198/6
  - Corbera, [posters on wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 177_198007)
    Moscow Number: 5/198/7
  - [15th IB banners and portrait on a wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 177_198011)
    Moscow Number: 5/198/11
  - [Free-standing information board; "Frente Movil, Timon Martillo (?)"], undated (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 177_198012)
    Moscow Number: 5/198/12